xl.com 2002-12-06

# Lucent - Privacy Statement

Lucent Technologies privacy statement

Lucent Technologies Inc. has long recognized that individuals with whom we conduct business value their privacy. However, in order to conduct global business in this increasingly electronic economy, the collection of personal information is often necessary and desirable. It is Lucent's goal to balance the benefits of e-commerce with the right of individuals to prevent the misuse of their personal information. 

The collection of personal information  
In some circumstances, Lucent may request personal information from you, like your name, e-mail address, company name, or telephone number. Your response to these inquiries is strictly voluntary. Lucent uses this information to customize your experience on our Web site. In addition, Lucent may use this information for other business purposes, such as to alerting you to products and services that can assist you in your business, promoting site registration, and assisting in order processing. 

In general, you can visit our site without divulging any personal information. However, there are areas of this site that require this information to complete their customization functions, and may not be available to those choosing not to reveal the information requested. 

Collecting domain information  
Lucent also collects domain information as part of its analysis of the use of this site. This data enables us to become more familiar with which customers visit our site, how often they visit, and what parts of the site they visit most often. Lucent uses this information to improve its Web-based offerings. This information is collected automatically and requires no action on your part. 

Disclosure to third parties  
In cases where we believe your business interests will be served, Lucent may share your information (with the exception of account, credit card, and ordering information) with Lucent BusinessPartners, who can alert you about new products and services to improve your competitive edge. If you receive unwanted marketing materials from any of our BusinessPartners, please let them know that you wish to be removed from their contact list. 

Use of cookies  
Some pages on this site use "cookies," which are small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. These files are used for site registration and customization the next time you visit us. You should note that cookies cannot read data off of your hard drive. Your Web browser may allow you to be notified when you are receiving a cookie, giving you the choice to accept it or not. By not accepting cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site. 

Lucent Technologies reserves the right to change, modify, or update this statement at any time without notice.
